Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Graduation and Reunion, 1900-1942
  - Reunion
    - Reunion — Class of 1882 in the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 30 [package161b])
    - Reunion — Class of 1890 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 30 [package161i])
    - Reunion — Class of 1890 in the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 29 [package159b])
    - Reunion — Class of 1890 in the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 30 [package161c])
    - Reunion — Class of 1891 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 29 [package159f])
    - Reunion — Class of 1909 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 27 [package151g])
    - Reunion — Class of 1911 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 27 [package151b])
    - Reunion — Class of 1911 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 27 [package151c])
    - Reunion — Class of 1911 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 27 [package151d])
    - Reunion — Class of 1912 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 30 [package161d])
    - Reunion — Helen D. Woodward and Harriette Warner Bishop, both Class of 1867 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 30 [package161e])
    - Reunion — Helen D. Woodward and Harriette Warner Bishop, both Class of 1867 at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 30 [package161f])
    - Reunion — Helen D. Woodward and Harriette Warner Bishop, both Class of 1867, and an unidentified woman at the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun 11 (Box 29 [package159])
    - Reunion — Class of 1909 in the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun11 (Box 29 [package159g])
    - Reunion — Class of 1910 in the Alumnae Parade, 1932 Jun11 (Box 29 [package159d])
    - Reunion — Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 7 [Package027_002])
    - Reunion — Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 7 [Package027_005])
    - Reunion — Class of 1886 at the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 7 [Package027_001])
    - Reunion — Class of 1886 in the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package026_001])
    - Reunion — Class of 1906 at the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package026_004])
    - Reunion — Class of 1906 in the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 7 [Package027_003])
    - Reunion — Class of 1906 in the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 7 [Package027_004])
    - Reunion — Class of 1907 at the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package026_003])
    - Reunion — Class of 1907 in the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 7 [Package027_006])
    - Reunion — Class of 1908 in the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package026_002])
    - Reunion — Class of 1918 in the Alumnae Parade, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package026_005])
- Series V. Drama, Music and Dance, 1900-1936
  - Student dancers — Copy photograph of a group of costumed dancers posing outside, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_018])
  - Two students in costume — Copy photograph of two students posed outside in costume, presumably for a skit or play, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_017])
  - Unidentified play — Copy photograph of a group of students in costume on steps, possibly for a Sophomore Party. Some have hockey sticks and baseball bats, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_019])
  - Third Hall Play — "Le Bourgeois Gentilhomme,", 1901 Mar 23 (Box 90 [Box248_005])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Critic,", 1914 Mar 7 (Box 63/64 [204_25])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Critic,", 1914 Mar 7 (Box 64 [205_22])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Critic,", 1914 Mar 7 (Box 64 [205_23])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 63/64 [204_01])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 63/64 [204_02])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 63/64 [204_12])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 63/64 [204_13])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 63/64 [204_19])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 65 [206_18])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 65 [206_24])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 66/67 [209_18])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 66/67 [209_19])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 66/67 [209_20])
  - Third Hall Play — "A Midsummer Night's Dream,", 1914 May (Box 87 [Box244_020])
  - Sophomore Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1918, including Edna St Vincent Millay (center in light-colored gown and cape) as the Princess of Pretencia. A student in brownface and a turban is visible in the group behind her., 1914 Oct 26 (Box 81 [236_15])
  - Sophomore Party — Full cast of skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1918. Several students in dark makeup can be seen in the right side of the image, 1914 Oct 26 (Box 81 [236_16])
  - Sophomore Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1918, 1914 Oct 26 (Box 81 [236_24])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1916 to the Class of 1918, 1914 Oct 31 (Box 77 [228_14])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1916 to the Class of 1918, 1914 Oct 31 (Box 77 [228_15])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1916 to the Class of 1918, 1914 Oct 31 (Box 77 [228_21])
  - Junior Party — Full cast of skit show presented by the Class of 1916 to the Class of 1918, 1914 Oct 31 (Box 77/78 [229_21])
  - First Hall Play — "The Piper,", 1914 Nov 7 (Box 73/74 [222_01])
  - First Hall Play — "The Piper,", 1914 Nov 7 (Box 73/74 [222_03])
  - First Hall Play — "The Piper,", 1914 Nov 7 (Box 74/75 [224_04])
  - Alumnae Play — "Vassar Milestones,", 1915 (Box 79 [232_19])
  - Alumnae Play — "Vassar Milestones,", 1915 (Box 79 [232_20])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Sylvette, 1915 Feb 27 (Box 80/81 [235_13])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Sylvette, 1915 Feb 27 (Box 80/81 [235_19])
  - First Minor Hall Play — "Land of Heart's Desire,", 1915 Mar 15 (Box 96/97 [Box257_017])
  - First Minor Hall Play — "Land of Heart's Desire,", 1915 Mar 15 (Box 96/97 [Box257_018])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_02])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_03])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_04])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_07])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_08])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_09])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 64 [205_10])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 66 [208_07])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 66 [208_08])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 66 [208_09])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 96/97 [Box257_001])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 96/97 [Box257_002])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 96/97 [Box257_004])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 97 [Box258_004])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida" with Edna St Vincent Millay as Eugene Marchbanks, 1915 Mar 5 (Box 97 [Box258_024])
  - Second Minor Hall Play — "Rosalie,", 1915 Apr 25 (Box 79 [232_21])
  - Third Hall Play — "Medea,", 1915 May 7 (Box 63/64 [204_04])
  - Third Hall Play — "Medea,", 1915 May 7 (Box 63/64 [204_22])
  - Third Hall Play — "Medea,", 1915 May 7 (Box 66/67 [209_10])
  - Third Hall Play — "Medea,", 1915 May 7 (Box 66/67 [209_11])
  - Sophomore Party — "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 81 [236_17])
  - Sophomore Party — "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 81 [236_23])
  - Sophomore Party — "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 95 [Box255_001])
  - Sophomore Party — "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 95 [Box255_002])
  - Sophomore Party — Full cast of "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 95 [Box255_004])
  - Sophomore Party — "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 95 [Box255_024])
  - Sophomore Party — "We're Roaming Through the Past To-night," a skit show set in the 1870s presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Oct 30 (Box 95 [Box255_025])
  - Junior Party — Class of 1919, most costumed as the pantomime character Pierrot, at the skit show presented to them by the Class of 1917, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 77/78 [229_01])
  - Junior Party — Class of 1919, most costumed as the pantomime character Pierrot, at the skit show presented to them by the Class of 1917, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 78 [230_03])
  - Junior Party — Italian street scene from the "Carnival of Nations" skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 78 [230_12])
  - Junior Party — Scene from the "Carnival of Nations" skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 78 [230_13])
  - Junior Party — American south scene from "Carnival of Nations," a skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1919. The scene includes 15 students in blackface, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 78 [230_14])
  - Junior Party — Japanese play scene from the "Carnival of Nations" skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 78 [230_22])
  - Junior Party — Scotland scene from the "Carnival of Nations" skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 78 [230_23])
  - Junior Party — Japanese play scene from the "Carnival of Nations" skit show presented by the Class of 1917 to the Class of 1919, 1915 Nov 6 (Box 89 [Box247_003])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 73/74 [222_05])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 73/74 [222_08])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 74/75 [224_05])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 74/75 [224_06])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 74/75 [224_07])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 74/75 [224_08])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 74/75 [224_15])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 74/75 [224_16])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 78/79 [231_20])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 78/79 [231_21])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 78/79 [231_22])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_014])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_015])
  - First Hall Play — "The Melting Pot,", 1915 Dec 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_016])
  - Faculty children's play — May be the May 1916 outdoor production of "The Lost Prince" acted by children of the Vassar faculty, approximately 1916 (Box 59 [package145])
  - Faculty children's play — May be the May 1916 outdoor production of "The Lost Prince" acted by children of the Vassar faculty, approximately 1916 (Box 59 [package145b])
  - Faculty children's play — May be the May 1916 outdoor production of "The Lost Prince" acted by children of the Vassar faculty, approximately 1916 (Box 59 [package145c])
  - Faculty children's play — May be the May 1916 outdoor production of "The Lost Prince" acted by children of the Vassar faculty, approximately 1916 (Box 59 [package145d])
  - Outdoor play — Unidentified outdoor play, 1916 (Box 79 [232_22])
  - Outdoor play — Unidentified outdoor play, 1916 (Box 87 [Box244_017])
  - Outdoor play — Unidentified outdoor play, 1916 (Box 90 [Box248_001])
  - Outdoor play — Unidentified outdoor play, 1916 (Box 98 [Box259_008])
  - French Club play — Outdoor performance of a play put on by the French Club, 1916-1917 (Box 79/80 [233_08])
  - French Club play — Outdoor performance of a play put on by the French Club, 1916-1917 (Box 84/85 [Box241_017])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 66 [208_11])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 66 [208_12])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 66 [208_13])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 66 [208_14])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_003])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_005])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_006])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_007])
  - Second Hall Play — "Deirdre of the Sorrows" with Edna St Vincent Millay, 1916 Mar 11 (Box 96/97 [Box257_008])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1918, 1916 May (Box 75/76 [226_23])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1918, 1916 May (Box 84/85 [Box241_001])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1918, 1916 May (Box 84/85 [Box241_002])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1918, 1916 May (Box 84/85 [Box241_003])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1918, 1916 May (Box 84/85 [Box241_019])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1918, 1916 May (Box 84/85 [Box241_020])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Class of 1918's Class Tree with medallion, 1916 May (Box 98 [Box259_023])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 97 [Box258_018])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 97 [Box258_019])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 97 [Box258_020])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 97 [Box258_021])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 98 [Box259_010])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 98 [Box259_011])
  - Latin class play — "Half Hour on Horace's Sabine Farm" by Esther Whitmarsh (VC 1918), 1916 May 19 (Box 98 [Box259_012])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 69 [213_09])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 69 [213_10])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 69 [213_24])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 85/86 [Box242_020])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 85/86 [Box242_021])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 85/86 [Box242_022])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 88/89 [Box246_014])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 88/89 [Box246_015])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 88/89 [Box246_024])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 89 [Box247_001])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 89 [Box247_004])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 89 [Box247_006])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 89 [Box247_007])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 89 [Box247_008])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 90 [Box248_023])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 90 [Box248_024])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 97 [Box258_009])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 97 [Box258_010])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 97 [Box258_011])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 97 [Box258_012])
  - Founder's Day play — One of a number of plays and dances put on for Founder's Day, 1916 May 5 (Box 97 [Box258_013])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 66/67 [209_04])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 66/67 [209_05])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 66/67 [209_06])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 84/85 [Box241_022])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 84/85 [Box241_023])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 87/88 [Box245_025])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 90 [Box248_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 90 [Box248_022])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 94 [Box254_001])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 94 [Box254_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 94 [Box254_004])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 94 [Box254_005])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 94 [Box254_006])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Tempest,", 1916 May 6 (Box 98 [Box259_025])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 62 [201_25])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, some in dark makeup, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 84 [Box240_010])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 84/85 [Box241_024])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 87/88 [Box245_004])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 87/88 [Box245_024])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_003])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. The group includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, some in dark makeup, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_004])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_006])
  - Sophomore Party — Flag Shop scene from "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_007])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, some in dark makeup, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_019])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_020])
  - Sophomore Party — "New Lamps for Old," a skit show centered around "Arabian Nights" presented by the Class of 1919 to the Class of 1920. This scene includes students in stereotypical Middle Eastern costumes, 1916 Nov 11 (Box 90 [Box248_021])
  - Junior Party — Full cast of the "Alices in Blunderland" skit show presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 18 (Box 62 [201_24])
  - Junior Party — "Alices in Blunderland" skit show presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 18 (Box 73 [221_02])
  - Junior Party — "Alices in Blunderland" skit show presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 18 (Box 73 [221_13])
  - Junior Party — "Alices in Blunderland" skit show presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 18 (Box 75 [225_09])
  - Junior Party — "Alices in Blunderland" skit show presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 18 (Box 87/88 [Box245_023])
  - Junior Party — "Alices in Blunderland" skit show presented by the Class of 1918 to the Class of 1920, 1916 Nov 18 (Box 93/94 [Box253_001])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_03])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_04])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_05])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_06])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff. This scene was set in Hawaii and features stereotypical costumes including grass skirts and dark makeup, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_07])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_08])
  - Thanksgiving Community Party — Skits, music and dance performed by faculty, students and staff. This scene features students and faculty in stereotypical Native American costumes, 1916 Nov 30 (Box 75 [225_10])